Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org
We're coming off of a long day
We got a taste of the wrong way, love
I'm looking over the storm break
But you got a thing
For the hard stuff…
Alex.
Jackie?
The other night,
that was a… a one-time thing.
Yeah, I guess we just, uh,
got caught up in the moment.
Right.
And we should just move past it. Agreed?
Yeah. Yeah.
It'll never happen…
But I know that you're sweet
When we sing that part
Oh, oh
Oh…
So that's what can never happen again.
Okay.
Oh…
I should get ready for school.
Yes, uh, same.
Oh
Stubborn
Why gotta be so stubborn?
Oh
Hi.
-Hey, morning. Good timing.
-French toast again?
Weren't you and Alex
supposed to have left by now?
Yes, thank you for asking.
And you, Nathan,
if you would like to get up first thing
and cook breakfast for everybody,
then you can make whatever
your little heart desires.
-Yum! French toast again.
-That's what I thought.
-Thank you, honey.
-You're welcome.
-Hey, morning.
-Morning.
Jackie. Listen, have you seen Alex?
I have to drop him off before work.
Now we're both gonna be late.
Me? No, I haven't seen Alex in ages.
Oh.
Hey, there you are! Go. Jump in the car.
Okay, and Nathan,
you are on dishwashing duty.
You take the kids to school.
Jackie, do you mind…
-Finish the lunches? On it.
-Yes. Thank you.
Okay.
Bye, guys. Have a good day.
Hey, uh, Jackie, Cole's got a meeting
with Miss Jacobs first thing, so we gotta…
Yup, okay.
I'll finish. Go ahead.
The, uh, apron's still on.
Have a good day, guys.
Try to learn something.
Benny, Jordan, Parker, five minutes!
We gotta go!
I said we had to leave early today.
-You can take shotgun.
-You have longer legs.
You're always
the first two ready and waiting
except the one day
I have to get to school early?
Yeah, but now you're making us later.
Ah. Good morning. Come on in.
Please. I'm not sure
you've ever asked to see me before, Cole.
I'm intrigued.
Does this have anything to do
with your probation?
No, it's just a few more hours
of community service, and it's done.
Good. Coach Allen
had to pull a lot of strings
to keep you and Dylan
from getting suspended.
I know.
I actually wanted
to talk about college applications.
That's great, Cole.
Okay, uh, let me just pull up your files.
Wow. Summer school performance was good.
-And you took your SATs a few weeks ago?
-Yeah.
Do you have any idea
where you might want to apply?
Well, I've been looking into
some coaching programs.
So maybe aim for some schools
where that's a major.
There are a few places
with really strong coaching programs.
They all have around the same minimum GPA,
and your GPA is…
Summer school definitely
brought your scores up,
but with everything
that happened junior year,
some of these colleges
might… might be a bit out of reach.
So basically what you're saying is
I dug myself a hole so deep,
I can't get out.
No, Cole, I did not say that.
Let's see what your SAT scores look like
when they come in
and your first semester grades.
A strong fall could pull you through in
the last quarter.
And isn't that the Cole Walter specialty?
Not anymore.
Thank you, Miss Jacobs.
-You're late.
-Yeah, sorry, I--
I thought we were cool.
If you're second-guessing things then--
I'm not, I swear. We are cool.
-So what horse did I draw?
-You were supposed to pick fourth.
But they won't let coaches draw,
so now there's only one horse left.
-Guess which one?
-Don't say it.
-True North.
-The horse that killed a man?
That's just a rumor, but you need
to be completely focused tomorrow.
-Or he might make you the first.
-I promise I will be 100% focused.
It'll be great.
You can take that down.
No. Never.
I'm gonna change it to say
"Student Body President" next year.
I still can't believe Paige won.
Maybe she'll surprise us and be great.
So far, the only thing she's done
is lobby for class presidents
to get designated parking spots.
I just really wanted to make a difference.
I sent Paige an email
with suggestions for future projects
like tutoring programs,
attending PTA meetings,
that kind of thing, but no response yet.
If you could do anything from that list,
what would it be?
Well, I really wanted
to build up the college fair,
bring in more colleges,
invite trade schools for kids
who don't wanna do the traditional route.
There's nothing that says you can't.
You just have to convince Miss Jacobs.
And so even though
I wasn't elected junior class president,
I wanna make sure the college fair--
Yes.
-Yes to what?
-You can help me with the college fair.
I would really appreciate the support,
and I'm pretty sure I'm not gonna be able
to finish this salad until I agree.
Great.
One more thing.
Would you see if the reps
might be willing to stay longer
and conduct one-on-one meetings,
like mini interviews?
It's great for students
who can't spend the money to visit campus.
If you can get an estimate
of how many students
might be interested in doing that,
I'll reach out to the reps
and see what we can do.
-I will do that right now.
-Of course you will.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
I'll close the door.
Thank you.
May I?
Okay, this band already found a drummer.
Old.
Homecoming Huddle was weeks ago,
and…
there you go.
Do you want to be the first?
No.
I'm good.
Yeah
I'm gon' mess you up
Feeding off that summer love
I ain't got nobody like you
I'm gon' mess you up
Face to face, it breaks my heart
I ain't got nobody like you
You got the mind for it
The type to ride with it…
I, uh, thought you rode
on the other side of the ranch.
I… I… I do usually.
I thought you ran on that side.
Well, I should…
Yeah, I mean, I sh… should probably, um…
I don't mean to hurt you, I'll admit
Uh
I'm gon' mess you up
Feeding off that summer love
I ain't got nobody like you…
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to…
Well, I did.
Because to be honest, it's all
I've been thinking about since yesterday.
So…
It breaks my heart
I ain't got nobody like you
Nobody like you, yeah
Yeah
I ain't got nobody like you
Nobody like you
Yeah
I ain't got nobody like you
Hey.
-Parker made this for you.
-What?
For luck.
Oh my gosh, that's so sweet.
Remember, you need to be
completely focused today.
You already made it
harder by missing the draw.
There's no more room
for additional mistakes… or distractions.
Don't worry.
No mistakes. No distractions. I'm on it.
Well, make sure you stay that way.
I promised your mom I'd keep you alive
because for some reason
she likes having you around.
All right, I'm just gonna go
tell Parker thanks, then we can go.
I helped Parker make that bracelet,
so think of it as good luck from me too.
Why does that sound like
you're not coming?
I'm not. I don't wanna be one of those
distractions that could get you hurt.
-I want you there.
-Blake's right. You need to focus.
Okay, if you really
don't think you should come.
I really don't.
Oh, hey, I just need to go get changed,
then I will be ready to get my rodeo on.
Okay, sounds great.
-Honey.
-Yeah?
Hey. Alex is gonna be fine today.
Of course he is.
I mean, he's been training like crazy,
and Blake's amazing.
I mean, she's totally safety first,
which is great.
-And you are--
-I'm kind of freaking out.
Yeah, I know.
-I'll be there.
-Oh.
Probably freaking out with you,
but I'll be there.
He's gonna be fine.
Come in.
Hi, sorry. I know it's Saturday.
Okay, we're just leaving for Alex's rodeo.
Is everything okay?
Not really.
There's a problem with the farm zoning.
It's holding up the permit,
which is tying the hands of my contact.
Can't this wait until Monday?
It can't. The only reason
we might be able to fix this
is because it's Saturday.
By Monday, it'll be too late.
Okay, I'll go, you stay.
-What? No.
-No, it's fine.
-I'll be fine, and I'll keep in touch.
-But I don't want to miss this.
I understand, but this is important.
Okay, I'll text Alex.
Hey, when you see him, will you at least
just let him know I'm rooting for him.
Of course.
I'm sorry.
The good life with me
Spitfire, roughneck
Don't need no husband
But, honey, I want ya
Right here next to me
I like being alone
I can hold my own
'Cause you're the kind of man
That I can see…
So this is part of our probation, huh?
Picking up trash here
in front of all these people.
Seriously?
Coach said this is it.
After today, we get a clean slate.
We better.
Start over by the kettle corn?
Lead the way.
Hello, fans, friends, and family,
and welcome to the Dubeau Valley Rodeo.
We are so excited to have all of you
in attendance here today.
So first things first, we gotta see
what kind of crowd we're dealing with.
All right, everybody,
let me hear you make some noise.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Dubeau Valley
and the DVR youth rodeo group
thank each and every one of you
for supporting the Colorado youth.
A big thank you to everyone
for your support.
True North, huh?
-You know he killed a guy?
-It's just a rumor.
Is it?
True North is tough for sure.
But as long as Alex keeps his nerve,
he'll be fine.
Might even beat you, Wylder.
Yeah, I doubt that.
I'm looking forward
to seeing you in the arena.
If what Blake says is true, then I might
just have me some real competition.
Enjoy the ride, Walter.
When the county surveyed the fire damage,
they discovered half the ranch
was improperly zoned,
which could mean
no rebuilding of any kind.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But I sweet-talked our new friend
in the permits department,
and he said if we get the rebuilding plans
into his office this weekend,
he'll backdate and approve them.
Okay.
Will and I went over
the expansion plans, but…
Look, I still don't know
that this is the right way to go.
It just feels too soon
to be making a decision this big.
We have to do it
before the offices open on Monday
to avoid a zoning commission review.
Richard's contact is doing us a solid here
because once they open
that official review--
We'll be stuck in red tape
for who knows how long.
And there's one more thing.
Because he's backdating the permits,
we have to promise to break ground
on the barn by the end of the month.
-At the end of this month?
-We can pull it together by then.
It's not a big deal.
Guys, these are huge changes.
Like, we need more time to finesse them,
make sure they work for us.
This is all just…
it's just moving way too fast.
I need time to think about this,
and I gotta talk to Katherine.
Okay. Um…
-Let's take five.
-Yeah.
Okay, look, I'm not gonna be forced
into making a quick decision on this
because there's
a hang-up in the permits office.
I'm gonna take as long as I need.
We'll weigh our options before we
start tearing everything up out there.
So I was thinking the paper
should interview some of the reps,
maybe get the inside scoop on what
the colleges are really looking for?
Thank you.
Okay, I'm just talking to myself,
aren't I?
Hmm?
No, yeah, I love that idea.
Just repeat it one more time.
I was saying the paper
can interview some of the reps maybe.
Juniors and seniors
would really appreciate it…
And here's Wylder Holt, three-time winner
of this event and a real rider to watch.
Did somebody order
some cheap white wine in a plastic cup?
Yes, this girl. Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for coming.
I know it was last-minute.
Honestly, I feel like I might've barfed
if I had to watch Alex by myself.
No, it's okay. Honestly,
it was nice to get out of the house.
How are things with Bob?
But you will have to tell me
how this event works.
Well, it's actually pretty simple.
Um, when that gate opens,
a 2,000-pound, very angry bucking horse
gets released into the arena
and tries to hurl the rider off
while they hold on
with one hand.
Super fun especially for moms.
Here's Wylder Holt,
three-time winner of this event
and a real rider to watch.
And he's out.
Oh my, this guy is frosty as a snowman,
and it shows.
Oh-ho! And there he goes!
What a ride for Wylder.
It's a full eight seconds for Wylder Holt.
-Wow.
-And a near perfect ride.
That's 83 points
for Wylder Holt, everybody.
That's really good.
-Is that good? Yeah.
-Yeah.
-Kind of.
-So that's…
Real competition for Alex.
Oh.
Put your hands together
for the one, the only, Wylder Holt!
And on deck, we have Alex Walter
riding True North, round one.
I competed here last week.
The soil is packed pretty loose,
so be prepared for that.
Remember to go with the horse,
even when you think you might be thrown.
You'll be good.
-And of course…
-I got this.
…a big thank you
to the Rescue Rangers themselves.
Put your hands together
for this year's pickup men.
-I got us doubles.
-Oh.
You're such a good friend.
-Thank you. That's my girl.
-Okay.
And now riding True North,
it's Alex Walter.
The first appearance for young Walter
in the Saddle Bronc Event,
although he has had strong showings
in the Extreme Cowboy Event.
-Okay.
There he goes.
True North is a tough horse. That horse
bucks like nothing else out here.
Oh!
And Walter's looking kind of shaky.
-Oh.
-Oh God.
And it's all over.
Alex Walter not able to hang on here
in round number one.
-He's okay.
-Yeah.
-He's gonna kill me.
He'll be disappointed.
I didn't realize you were so into rodeo.
Yeah, well,
it's a big part of life around here,
so it feels like I should be.
How are you doing?
Feeling any better about Nathan?
I'm fine.
I forgot sugar. I'll be right back.
Okay, what is going on?
Me and Alex have been, you know…
Oh, you're back together?
No. I don't know.
It probably means nothing.
Well, does it mean nothing to you?
I don't know what it means, except that
I need to stay away from the rodeo today.
Alex needs to be focused, and I would
never forgive myself if he got hurt.
Okay.
But what do you want to do right now?
-I want to go to the rodeo.
-And what does Alex want you to do?
He wants me to go to the rodeo.
Right. So if you want to go to the rodeo,
and Alex wants you to go to the rodeo…
Oh, hello.
I was gone for like three seconds.
Spill. What did I miss?
How do you feel about hot cowboys
and all-you-can-eat snacks? My treat.
I'm single now.
Let's be real. You had me at hot cowboys.
I have this cute top
I've been, like, dying to wear.
Slay.
-Should we go?
-Yeah.
-What the hell was that?
-I know.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened. Okay?
I know True North is challenging,
but you're making mistakes
you've never made before.
-I think the cinches were coming loose.
-Is it because I'm here?
I thought we were cool
with me staying your coach.
That's not it.
It's amazing that you're here.
I… I'm sorry, okay?
I don't know what happened.
You know horses can sense your mood.
You still have one more round.
Do you trust yourself to be all in?
Yeah.
I do.
Okay.
Next out of the chute,
we have Tanner Jones, everybody.
And there he goes, folks.
He's looking strong and steady!
Look at that cowboy go, folks.
We need to make sure
you're making noise as he goes around.
No, I agree with you.
If they're going too far too fast,
then we have to push back.
Yeah, it's not what we wanted.
Okay. We can talk about it more tonight.
Bye. I'm sorry. That was George.
-No problem. I remembered you were sweet.
-Yeah.
Not salty.
Um, so there's another round?
Yeah, we get to do this all over again.
I can't believe I agreed to this.
The idea of another one
of my kids getting hurt.
Another one? You mean Cole?
That was two years ago.
That wasn't your fault.
Yeah, but I let him go skiing.
I mean, I can't help but think
even if I'd just said no
or maybe if I'd gone with him,
the accident wouldn't have happened?
Look, motherhood is 90% guilt and fear.
Yeah. And laundry.
I don't know how you do it.
Do what?
Well, just let them take chances
and make mistakes.
Oh, believe me,
I don't always have a choice.
Yeah, but I just wish
I was a little more like that with Grace.
I just don't ever want to let her go.
I get it.
Oh.
Here.
Did you see the one that fell?
That poor kid.
Blake likes to take risks
on the riders she coaches.
That Alex guy turned out
to be a real waste of time.
I bet the two seconds he stayed on
the bronc was a personal best for the kid.
What about that Tanner Jones?
Hey, Wylder, you might want
to watch your mouth.
You're talking shit
next to somebody's brother.
Hey, look, no offense.
He's all right,
but if he keeps riding like that,
he's gonna end up hurt or worse.
Riding broncs ain't for everybody.
He should stick to something
more his pace. No shame in it.
Okay, assuming we break ground
in a couple weeks, we're gonna need…
Yeah.
George.
You… you guys have to know
that this isn't what we agreed on.
Right? The project was always
supposed to work alongside the ranch,
and it's… it's completely taken over.
Yes, this is more than we first discussed,
but expanding means
that we can maximize our potential.
Uh…
And look, I've really thought about it,
and I've thought about
how much this land means to our family,
and I just don't think
that this is the right way to go.
I'm… I'm sorry you feel that way, George,
but there's a lot at stake here.
I understand.
If we don't move forward immediately,
we could all lose out.
I've already lost out, Richard.
I lost the barn that my kids played in,
that I played in.
My great-grandfather's shed
no longer sits on the site
that he built it 100 years ago.
And right now, I'm missing
my son's first bronc riding competition.
I…
I just… I don't…
I don't wanna lose anymore.
Dad, we're gonna make sure
that doesn't happen.
Will, this is my property,
and I have final say.
I'm really sorry, but it stops here.
George, I… I'm gonna be straight with you.
I really want you on board.
But if we can't agree on a way forward,
the contract states that I have a right
to assume control of the project
to ensure its financial well-being.
It says what?
Is that right?
Yeah. There's a clause.
You would cut us out of this project?
Make decisions about our land without us?
Only if I had no choice.
I'm sure that this contract
probably also said this was originally
just supposed to be tents.
It's probably not
as watertight as you think.
George, I don't want it to come to that.
-Then you shouldn't have threatened me.
-I'm not.
Dad, we just have to figure out
a way to make this work, okay?
I would like for you to leave.
You know,
I'm sure we can figure this out.
Will?
I'll call you later, Dad.
Wow!
What a view.
I know.
-They're so pretty.
-Do you know?
-I'll be right back.
-Okay. Well, take your time.
We'll just be here drinking in all the…
Wait. Jackie, give me your jacket, please,
before my mom sees.
Too late.
It's okay.
Just, uh, go wish Alex good luck.
I'll be here, quietly dying.
-Hey.
Thanks for coming out.
Are you sure it's okay?
I know you don't want any distractions,
but I didn't wanna miss that moment
when you ride that bronc
for the full eight seconds.
Well,
you obviously didn't see my first ride
or you would not be this confident.
Actually, I did see it on the live stream.
That's why I came.
I just wanted to tell you that I…
I know what a great rider you are.
And I know you can do this.
You just have to ride
like you know it too.
Next up, Alex Walter in his second round.
Uh…
Wish me luck?
You don't need luck.
You're gonna be great.
Look. Look who's here.
Hi.
-Sorry.
-So good to see you.
-How's it going?
-Okay.
Hi.
I didn't know Jackie was coming.
Yeah.
I'm glad she's here.
It's okay.
Yeah.
We're back with Alex Walter
after a near wipeout in round one.
Let's see if he can make up his points
here in round two.
And he's out!
He's looking strong, folks.
Look at Alex Walter go!
It's a brand-new rider, everybody.
True North's giving it everything,
but Alex is holding strong!
Whoa!
That was something else, folks.
Let's hear it for Alex Walter!
Whoo!
And that's a score of 81 for Alex Walter!
Yes!
Okay, so we're gonna go see him.
Do you want to come?
I'm gonna go and chat with Grace,
but you should be so proud.
That was amazing.
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
Okay, bye.
Okay, see you later.
See ya. Bye.
I gotta get back to picking up trash.
Tell Alex congratulations.
At least one Walter is a success.
Okay, well, Alex isn't the only success
in our family. You know that.
You won't say that
after you see my SAT scores.
Cole.
I studied for months,
and it still wasn't enough.
You can take them again.
Mom, without football
or without a time machine
to go back and fix last year,
I think college or…
or any type of real future
is off the table for a while.
No, you know what?
I'll be fine.
Just go tell Alex
how proud we all are of him.
Cole, let me ask you something.
Was I proud of the star quarterback Cole?
Of course!
You were always a natural athlete,
and football came easily to you.
But the guy that's standing here now,
creating his life from scratch
with hard work,
after everything he's been through,
I'm so much more proud of that Cole.
You're gonna want
to give me a hug, aren't you?
I think this is more embarrassing
than trash duty now.
Listen to me.
No matter what direction your life takes,
no matter what you end up doing,
your father and I couldn't be more proud
or more grateful that you are our son.
Okay?
-Okay?
-Okay.
-Okay. Okay.
I love this face.
Okay, go on before I hug you again.
And now,
for the Saddle Bronc Riding Division
of the 12 riders in the competition,
these are your top five.
Starting with number five,
it's Alex Walter!
Whoo!
Great job, Alex!
Not too bad!
And in first place,
for the fourth time
at the Dubeau Valley Rodeo,
with a hugely impressive score,
it's your champion, Wylder Holt!
Girl, I can't take my eyes off you
Yeah, we're learning to love
About everything we messed up…
Congratulations, Wylder.
Thanks.
That second round was a good ride.
You pulled it back out there.
That's not an easy thing to do.
Blake could be right about you.
Maybe I do have to watch my back.
I'll see you around, Alex Walter.
Yeah, see you.
Fifth out of 12,
that's a very strong debut.
How does it feel?
It feels like I won.
I couldn't have done
any of it without you.
Oh, I'm well aware of that.
You know, my dad asked about you today.
Okay, what does that mean?
My dad sponsors riders
all over the country.
So if he thinks you're good,
then you might have a future in this.
-Really?
-He's holding tryouts in a few weeks.
If you're interested,
he's looking for some new riders
to compete under his banner.
Wow, that's amazing.
Yeah, but he's very selective.
We'll need to put some work in,
but if you want to, then you could try.
Yeah! Yeah, I want to.
Okay, good. We'll work on that then.
I gotta go,
but I will text you about practice.
Monday 5:00 a.m.
-Blake.
-Yeah.
Seriously.
Thank you… for everything.
Anytime.
When you're right next to me
I wanna hold you close
Till this old bar closes…
Hey! Oh.
-Hey.
-Hi. I've been looking for you.
Nice top.
Yeah, um, I know.
I'm sorry. I'll get rid of it.
I…
I think you look beautiful.
But?
But nothing.
I think it's about time that I let you
make more of your own choices,
whether I like them or not.
But you might want to put on a sweater
before you come home.
We don't want to upset your father,
and I am not sure
that he is ready for this Grace just yet.
I love you.
I love you too.
Change my shirt and check my phone
Drive out where the sun goes down
My darling, can I tell you
That I can't stop this feel
Can't doubt what's real
You've made
My little old heart stand still
Oh my. Oh my.
Dude, I swear, I just cannot pick up
one more hot dog bun without getting high.
I mean, these people are animals.
The trash can is right there.
-What are we doing?
-Jesus.
Oh.
Hmm.
Forgetting this entire day
would… be, uh…
Well,
you have the power
in your hands, young Jedi.
We text all night
Till the break of dawn
Counting down those days…
I'm good.
It's all you.
I can't stop this feel
Can't stop what's real…
Okay, then.
Just, uh… don't get so high
these hot dog buns we've been picking up
start looking like snacks. Yeah?
Yeah, I, uh… I make no promises.
Okay.
-Oh, hey.
-Can I have an autograph?
-Stop.
Now that you're a big rodeo star,
I wasn't sure what was less embarrassing,
that or a hug.
Um, Mom, I placed fifth.
It's not like I won.
It is to me,
but I'm never gonna get used to
seeing you thrown off a horse like that.
Well, uh, sorry
because Blake thinks
her dad might wanna sponsor me,
and if so, I'll be competing a lot more.
So that means I have to…
Watch me get thrown off a horse again?
-Yeah.
-But not that horse, right?
-That horse was horrifying.
-God, no.
-Like from the apocalypse.
-Yeah.
-Terrifying.
You looked really good out there, bud.
I mean, I'm terrified for me, but…
I am so happy for you
that you found your passion.
It shows.
Come here. Come here.
Oh.
-I love you.
-I love you too.
-Thanks for coming.
-Anytime.
What's going on?
Richard threatened to cut me out
of the guest ranch project.
How can I help you fix this?
I found this vine,
out when I was looking for Murphy.
And it turns out,
we used to have a vineyard out there,
and a pretty damn good one
from what I read.
Okay, so what's the plan?
You still play golf with Victoria Chase
from Little Cap Winery?
Yeah.
I'd love to sit down with her.
I'll set it up.
Thank you, buddy.
Thanks for coming.
Those donuts were slammin'.
They were!
-This was great. I needed this.
-It was!
We'll see you at the car.
Did you see Alex?
I was so worried when he fell,
but then he got right back up.
Well, that's how we do it, right?
We just keep falling and getting back up.
Are we still talking about the rodeo?
I got my SAT scores back today.
And?
Well, you know, not every college
relies on SAT scores anymore.
Yeah, but my GPA has
basically tanked from last year.
Did summer school help?
Not enough.
What if I help?
This is what I'm good at.
I can make a study planner
for the SAT retakes,
and we can fill out applications together.
We'll get you into college. I promise.
Can't wait to get rid of me, huh?
No, of course not. I… I just…
I just want you to be happy.
I know.
Thank you.
Welcome to
the Jackie Howard College Bootcamp.
Um, Jackie, one… one more thing. Um…
Can we not tell anyone about this?
It's just I'm tired of being a failure,
of… of needing people
to step in all the time.
Can we keep it just between us?
Of course we can.
Just us.
-Hi.
-Hey.
I haven't been in here
since Cole let you move in.
Yeah, I know.
It's been really solid of him
to share his space with me like this.
I should thank him more.
Well, him and you.
Why me?
Because.
I wouldn't have been able to ride
that well if you hadn't been there.
I don't think that's true.
I just told you to trust yourself.
You would've been great anyway.
But being there, watching you ride,
watching you do something you love…
It was amazing,
and it made me happy.
You make me happy.
We said we wouldn't do that again.
Yeah, we did.
You know,
we keep trying not to be together,
and I'm not really sure I know why.
You do know why.
It's complicated.
Not for me.
Look, I know I said I needed time before,
but to be honest, I was miserable.
And now I'm not.
I want to be with you, Jackie.
But with everything that's happened…
Okay. Yeah, you're right.
Maybe it is a little complicated.
What if we didn't tell anyone?
Until we're sure.
For now it could be
just for us?
My hand as I wash…
Yeah.
Okay.
Just us.
Oh, what a day
It's come on to you
Oh, want to do it
It's so on to you
Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org